<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AI Imaging Lab</title>
    <description>School of Electronic Engineering, Xidian University</description>
    <link>https://jiminliang.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://jiminliang.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:54:26 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:54:26 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maintaining the website</title>
        <description>

My first blog!

I built this website using Jekyll on Windows 10. It cost me one week to build the framework and another week to fill the contents. I wrote the following tips in case I need to repeat the job sometimes in the future.



  Fundamentals
  Installation
  Build




Fundamentals
Github provides a simple way to build and host a static website or blogs. It surports Jelyll, a simple, extendable, static site generator, and markdown language to wirte the website pages.


  
    Basic knowledge about Github Pages. I used homepage in stead of username.github.io as the repository name of my website. In this case my website can be accessed at https://jiminliang.github.io/homepage/.
  
  
    Knowledge about Jekyll.
  
  Our website is based on the Project Pages template. I moved the blog page to an individual webpage, by adding the following line in _config.yml:
    paginate_path: &quot;/blog/page:10/&quot;
    
  
  For publication list, I used the bibjekyll plugin. On Windows, beside bibtex2html, you also need to install the bibtex.exe. I installed the CTEX packges to have it.


A more detailed description on how to maintain a website with Jekyll can be found here.

Installation

  
    Install Jekyll following comments here.
  
  Install jekyll-paginate plugin :
    gem install jekyll-paginate
    
  
  Install bibjekyll plugin following comments here and add the path of Bibtex2html to system path variable.


Build

  Preview locally ：
    jekyll serve
    
  
  Build to other directory ：
    jekyll build --destination ..\homepage
    
  
  Done. Publish it with Git.

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://jiminliang.github.io/skills/2018/09/04/Maintaining-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jiminliang.github.io/skills/2018/09/04/Maintaining-website/</guid>
        
        <category>How_to</category>
        
        
        <category>Skills</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
